A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Speech Files, RG 5 FA434
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Speech Files, 1941-2004; 5; 38 document box(es)
  - 1984
    - Statement in Support of H.R. 2837 and S. 1090 to Establish a National Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Committee, 1984 April 26 (Box 26, Folder 428)
      Statement made before United States House of Representatives, Subcommittee on Public Lands and National Parks, Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs.
    - Centennial Salutation, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1984 May 17 (Box 26, Folder 429)
    - Declination of Interview Request Regarding Staff Changes at Reader's Digest, 1984 May 21 (Box 26, Folder 430)
      Request for interview came from Miriam Lacob of the Columbia Journalism Review.
    - Henry Kissinger-Osteopathy Luncheon, New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, 1984 May 30 (Box 26, Folder 431)
    - Toast to Governor John D. Rockefeller IV, Candidate for U.S. Senate, 1984 June 10 (Box 26, Folder 433)
      Fundraising event held at Kykuit.
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony for Nathan Cummings Center, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1984 June 13 (Box 26, Folder 434)
    - Dedication of the Jack K. Lazar Admissions Center, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1984 June 20 (Box 26, Folder 435)
    - Retirement Tribute to Dr. Marguerite P. Sykes, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1984 June 21 (Box 26, Folder 436)
    - Establishment of Abby Rockefeller Mauzé Professorship, New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center, 1984 July 19 (Box 26, Folder 437)
    - 25 Years Service Awards, Wayfarer Ketch Corporation, 1984 September 21 (Box 26, Folder 438)
      Awards to Mal Doak, Frank Collins, and Leonard Kilinski.
    - Acceptance of the Degree Juris Doctor Honoris Causus, Vermont Law School, 1984 September 28-29 (Box 26, Folder 439)
    - Family Christmas Party, Toast to David Rockefeller, 1984 December 16 (Box 26, Folder 440)
  - 1985
    - Welcome of Jeanne Thayer as Chairman, Sleepy Hollow Restorations, 1985 June 4 (Box 26, Folder 432)
      Folder 432, Box 26, was mistakenly placed out of date order in the original finding aid. Although listed among "1984" speeches, it belongs in "1985" and has been listed as such in AT.
    - New York Zoological Society Annual Meeting, 1985 February 6 (Box 27, Folder 441)
    - JungleWorld Dedication, New York Zoological Society, 1985 June 21 (Box 27, Folder 442)
    - Unveiling of Lewis Thomas Portrait, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 February 13 (Box 27, Folder 443)
    - Fund Appeal Letters on Behalf of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 April 16-22 (Box 27, Folder 444)
      Letters to David Roderick, Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, U. S. Steel Corporation, and Lee Iacocca, Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, Chrysler Corporation.
    - Fund Appeal Letter on Behalf of Sleepy Hollow Restorations, 1985 April 17 (Box 27, Folder 445)
      Draft of letter to John Ackers, President of IBM Corporation.
    - Mary Lasker Testimonial Dinner, National Center for Health Education, 1985 May 16 (Box 27, Folder 446)
    - "The Night of the Wildflowers," National Wildflower Research Center Benefit, 1985 May 22 (Box 27, Folder 447)
    - 25-Year Tribute, Charles Browand, Room 5600, 1985 May 29 (Box 27, Folder 448)
    - Academic Convocation, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 May 30 (Box 27, Folder 449)
    - Academic Convocation, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 May 30 (Box 27, Folder 450)
      Folder contains research material.
    - Tribute to Jeanne Thayer, Sleepy Hollow Restorations, 1985 June 4 (Box 27, Folder 451)
    - Dedication of the DeWitt Wallace Decorative Arts Gallery, Colonial Williamburg, 1985 June 8 (Box 28, Folder 452)
      See also Folder 453.
    - Dedication of the DeWitt Wallace Decorative Arts Gallery, Colonial Williamsburg, 1985 June 8 (Box 28, Folder 453)
      See also Folder 452.
    - Twenty Year Club, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 June 19 (Box 28, Folder 454)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony, Research Scholar's Residence, Rockefeller University/Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 June 21 (Box 28, Folder 455)
    - Tribute to Nancy Hanks, Duke University, 1985 July 23 (Box 28, Folder 456)
    - 25-Year Tribute, Peter Crisp, Room 5600, 1985 July 30 (Box 28, Folder 457)
    - Dedication of John Mayer Parlor, Woodstock Historical Society, 1985 August 10 (Box 28, Folder 458)
    - Announcement of the Rockefeller Research Laboratories, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 August 13 (Box 28, Folder 459)
    - First Meeting of President's Commission on Americans Outdoors, 1985 September 13 (Box 28, Folder 460)
    - National Campaign Committee Meeting, Princeton University, 1985 September 27 (Box 28, Folder 461)
    - Venrock Company Chief Executive Officers, Room 5600, 1985 October 1 (Box 28, Folder 462)
    - Dedication of Magnetic Resonance Imaging Unit and Endowment of the Carroll and Milton Petrie Chair in Diagnostic Imaging, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 October 7 (Box 28, Folder 463)
    - Dedication of Nathan Cummings Center, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 October 11 (Box 28, Folder 464)
    - Sinatra '86 Kickoff Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 December 2 (Box 28, Folder 465)
    - Acceptance of New York Zoological Society Gold Medal, 1985 December 10 (Box 28, Folder 466)
      Medal commemorated 50 years as a Trustee of the New York Zoological Society.
  - 1986
    - National Council on Alcoholism, 1986 January 23 (Box 29, Folder 467)
    - Julia Parmly Billings Apse, University of Vermont, 1986 April 17 (Box 29, Folder 468)
    - Dedication of Lewis Thomas Laboratory, Princeton University, 1986 April 18 (Box 29, Folder 469)
    - Dedication of Rockefeller State Park Preserve, Pocantico Hills, 1986 May 2 (Box 29, Folder 470)
    - First Meeting, Central Park Perimeter Association, 1986 May 20 (Box 29, Folder 471)
    - Seventh Annual Academic Convocation, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1986 May 28 (Box 29, Folder 472)
    - Ground Breaking Ceremony, Rockefeller Research Laboratories, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1986 June 24 (Box 29, Folder 473)
    - Toast to President Ronald Reagan, Dinner at Pocantico, 1986 July 4 (Box 29, Folder 474)
      Visit coincided with the 100th anniversary of the Statue of Liberty and its relighting.
    - Signing of the 1986 Environmental Bond Issue, 1986 July 23 (Box 29, Folder 475)
    - Memorial Raffle Kickoff, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1986 September 18 (Box 29, Folder 476)
    - Highway Beautification Act, Correspondence, 1986 September 18 (Box 30, Folder 477)
    - Acceptance of Top Dog Award, The Animal Medical Center, 1986 November 11 (Box 30, Folder 478)
    - Saint Nicholas Dinner Dance, Sleepy Hollow Restorations, 1986 December 6 (Box 30, Folder 479)
  - 1987
    - Tribute to Benno Schmidt, Academic Convocation, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1987 May 26 (Box 30, Folder 480)
    - Service of Remembrance, Class of 1932, Princeton University, 1987 June 5 (Box 30, Folder 481)
    - Thoughts for Talk with California Associates, 1987 June 5 (Box 30, Folder 482)
    - Topping Off Reception, Rockefeller Research Laboratories, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1987 July 1 (Box 30, Folder 483)
    - Second Annual Meeting, Central Park Perimeter Association, 1987 September 29 (Box 30, Folder 484)
    - Historic Hudson Valley Dinner, 1987 November 2 (Box 30, Folder 485)
      First celebration of Historic Hudson Valley as successor to Sleepy Hollow Restorations.
    - Reception for Mr. and Mrs. Laurance S. Rockefeller, The University of Chicago Divinity School, 1987 November 10 (Box 30, Folder 486)
      Reception "in gratitude for the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Chair in the Philosophy of Comparative Religions."
    - Tribute to Jeanne Thayer, Historic Hudson Valley, 1987 December 4 (Box 30, Folder 487)
    - Rockefeller family: Christmas Party, 1987 December 13 (Box 30, Folder 488)
  - 1988
    - Second Venrock Conference: Welcoming Speech: Venture capital, 1988 May 10 (Box 30, Folder 489)
    - Lady Bird Johnson's Book Party, Old Westbury Gardens, 1988 June 7 (Box 31, Folder 490)
      Lady Bird Johnson's book entitled "Wildflowers Across America." See also Folder 490A.
    - Lady Bird Johnson's Book Party, Old Westbury Gardens, 1988 June 7 (Box 31, Folder 490A)
      Lady Bird Johnson's book entitled "Wildflowers Across America." See also Folder 490.
    - Interview by Sheila Holtzman, 1988 June 20 (Box 31, Folder 491)
      Scope and Contents
      Interview on the topic of LSR's business success, focusing in particular on his Rockresorts.
    - John E. Fetzer Foundation Global Conference, "Helping Heal the Whole Person and the Whole World", 1988 June 25 (Box 31, Folder 492)
      See also Folders 492A and 492B.
    - John E. Fetzer Foundation Global Conference, "Helping Heal the Whole Person and the Whole World", 1988 June 25 (Box 31, Folder 492A)
      See also Folders 492 and 492B.
    - John E. Fetzer Foundation Global Conference, "Helping Heal the Whole Person and the Whole World", 1988 June 25 (Box 31, Folder 492B)
      See also Folders 492 and 492A.
    - Toast to Dr. Samuel Hellman, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1988 June 27 (Box 32, Folder 493)
    - Presentation of Top Dog Award, The Animal Medical Center, 1988 November 16 (Box 32, Folder 494)
      Award presented by LSR to Mamdouha (Dodo) Bobst (Mrs. Elmer Holmes Bobst).
    - Introduction of Dr. Harold Shapiro, Princeton University Dinner at 834 Fifth Avenue, 1988 December 1 (Box 32, Folder 495)
  - 1989
    - Third Annual Meeting, Central Park Perimeter Association, 1989 January 12 (Box 32, Folder 496)
    - Press Conference, Central Park Conservancy, 1989 April 12 (Box 32, Folder 497)
      Presentation of $35 million raised in the capital campaign.
    - Dedication of Laurance S. Rockefeller Board Room, Rockefeller Research Laboratories, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1989 May 11 (Box 32, Folder 498A)
      See also Folder 498B.
    - Dedication of Laurance S. Rockefeller Board Room, Rockefeller Research Laboratories, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1989 May 11 (Box 32, Folder 498B)
      See also Folder 498A.
    - Dedication of the Rockefeller Research Laboratories, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1989 May 17 (Box 32, Folder 499A)
      Laboratories named in honor of John D. Rockefeller Jr. See also Folder 499B.
    - Dedication of the Rockefeller Research Laboratories, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1989 May 17 (Box 32, Folder 499B)
      Laboratories named in honor of John D. Rockefeller Jr. See also Folder 499A.
    - Dinner Dance in Honor of Mary and Laurance Rockefeller, The Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1989 June 5 (Box 33, Folder 500)
    - Tribute to Nash Castro, Executive Director, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1989 June 15 (Box 33, Folder 501)
    - Dedication of Benno C. Schmidt Conference Room, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1989 June 20 (Box 33, Folder 502)
    - 25 Year Service Awards, Wayfarer Ketch Corporation, 1989 July 7 (Box 33, Folder 503)
      Service awards presented to Dick D'Ambrogio and Paul Voorhees.
    - Rededication of Billings Farm and Museum, Woodstock Corporation, 1989 July 15-16 (Box 33, Folder 504)
    - Presentation to the Foreign Policy Association Board of Governors, Draft Copy, 1989 October 24 (Box 33, Folder 505)
      Presentation on Foreign Policy Association delegation trip to the U.S.S.R., September 27 to October 8, 1989.
    - John D. Rockefeller 150th Anniversary Conference, 1989 October 27 (Box 33, Folder 506)
    - W. Kenneth Riland Scholarship Luncheon, New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, 1989 December 6 (Box 33, Folder 507)
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates: Christmas Party, 1989 December 15 (Box 33, Folder 508)
  - 1990
    - Nash Castro Retirement Dinner, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1990 April 4 (Box 33, Folder 509)
    - Acceptance of Eighth Annual Frederick Law Olmstead Award, Women's Committee of the Central Park Conservancy, 1990 May 2 (Box 34, Folder 510)
    - Award to Benno C. Schmidt, Academic Convocation, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1990 May 23 (Box 34, Folder 511)
    - Senator John D. (Jay) Rockefeller IV Campaign Luncheon, Pocantico Hills, 1990 June 2 (Box 34, Folder 512)
    - Senator John D. (Jay) Rockefeller IV Campaign Luncheon, Pocantico Hills, 1990 June 2 (Box 34, Folder 512A)
    - Announcement of Jim and Mary Evans Horticultural Endowment Fund, Central Park Conservancy, 1990 June 8 (Box 34, Folder 513)
    - 25-Year Service Award to George R. Lamb, 1990 November 9 (Box 34, Folder 514)
    - Presentation of The Freedom of the Human Spirit Award, International Center for the Disabled, 1990 December 12 (Box 34, Folder 515)
      Awards presented to Mrs. H. Lawrence (Margie) Bogert, chairperson of ICD, and Jeremiah (Jerry) Milbank Jr., president of ICD.
  - 1991
    - Woodrow Wilson Award, Princeton University, 1991 February 16 (Box 34, Folder 516)
      Remarks entitled "Reflections on Princeton and Beyond."
    - Introduction of Dr. Deepak Chopra, Seminar on Quantum Healing, 1991 May 10 (Box 34, Folder 517)
    - William F. Pounds Retirement Dinner, 1991 May 13 (Box 35, Folder 518)
      Dinner held at the River Club.
    - Dedication of Barbara Hinman Memorial Plaque, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1991 May 23 (Box 35, Folder 519)
      Reception also honored Barbara Hinman's husband, George L. Hinman.
    - Retirement Dinner for George D. Taylor, Jr., Rockefeller Financial Services, 1991 June 19 (Box 35, Folder 520)
    - 40th Anniversary, Historic Hudson Valley, 1991 June 22 (Box 35, Folder 521)
    - Dedication of Enid A. Haupt Pavilion, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1991 July 24 (Box 35, Folder 522)
    - Remarks on the Proposed Marsh-Billings National Historical Park, Woodstock Public Hearing, 1991 August 12 (Box 35, Folder 523)
    - Acceptance of Congressional Gold Medal from President George Bush, 1991 September 27 (Box 35, Folder 524)
    - Introduction of Paul Volcker, Venrock Conference, Pocantico Hills, 1991 October 8 (Box 35, Folder 525)
    - Historic Hudson Valley Benefit Dinner, 1991 November 11 (Box 35, Folder 526)
  - 1992
    - U. S. Senate Hearing, Marsh-Billings National Historical Park, 1992 March 26 (Box 35, Folder 527)
    - Statement in Support of Marsh-Billings National Historical Park, U. S. House Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, Subcommittee on National Parks and Public Lands, 1992 June 2 (Box 35, Folder 528)
    - Historic Hudson Valley Summer Garden Party, Pocantico Hills, 1992 June 13 (Box 36, Folder 529)
    - Testimonial, National Wildflower Research Center's 10th Anniversary Newsletter, 1992 June 17 (Box 36, Folder 530)
    - Statement for Library Case Study, The Joseph Campbell Archives and Library, 1992 July 30 (Box 36, Folder 531)
    - Dinner Honoring Louis Marx, Princeton University, 1992 October 19 (Box 36, Folder 532)
      Remarks thanking Louis Marx for his "incredible perceptiveness and generosity to Princeton in making Marx Hall possible!"
    - Lady Bird Johnson's 80th Birthday Celebration, 1992 December 4 (Box 36, Folder 533)
  - 1993
    - Resignation from Board of Directors, The Reader's Digest, 1993 January 8 (Box 36, Folder 534)
    - Marsh-Billings Deed Transfer Ceremony, 1993 January 11 (Box 36, Folder 535)
    - Dedication of Louis Marx, Jr. '53 Hall, Princeton University, 1993 April 30 (Box 36, Folder 536)
    - Inauguration of Historic Hudson Valley Cruises, 1993 June 23 (Box 36, Folder 537)
    - 10th Anniversary Celebration, Billings Farm and Museum, 1993 July 25 (Box 36, Folder 538)
    - Reception for Laurance S. Rockefeller and the Fund for the Enhancement of the Human Spirit, 1993 September 25 (Box 36, Folder 539)
    - Announcement of "The Pocantico Society," Historic Hudson Valley Benefit, 1993 October 18 (Box 36, Folder 540)
    - Acceptance of 1993 Plymouth Committee Award, Society of Mayflower Descendants, 1993 November 5 (Box 36, Folder 541)
    - Opening of the Conservation Stewardship Workshop, Marsh-Billings Seminar, 1993 November 20 (Box 36, Folder 542)
  - 1994
    - Citizens Committee for New York City Awards, 1994 February 14 (Box 36, Folder 543)
      Mr. and Mrs. Laurance S. Rockefeller were one of four "Couples Who Care" to be awarded the New Yorker for New York Award.
    - The Pocantico Society, Historic Hudson Valley, 1994 May 25 (Box 36, Folder 544)
    - Response to Lady Bird Johnson's Toast, Scenic Hudson's "Spirit of the River Gala", 1994 June 1 (Box 36, Folder 545)
    - Statement for George Grune Retirement Video, The Reader's Digest, 1994 July 20 (Box 36, Folder 546)
      Video taped June 3, 1994.
    - The James Madison Council of the Library of Congress Dinner, 1994 June 8 (Box 36, Folder 547)
    - Dinner Honoring Their Majesties, the Emperor Akihito and Empress Michiko, 1994 June 16 (Box 36, Folder 548)
      The Emperor and Empress of Japan were honored at a dinner at Kykuit.
    - Dedication of Visitor Orientation, Rockefeller State Park Preserve, 1994 June 18 (Box 37, Folder 549)
    - Presentation of First John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Founder's Award, Historic Hudson Valley, 1994 November 8 (Box 37, Folder 550)
      Award presented to Richard H. Jenrette.
    - Links Breakfast Prayer, 1994 November 22 (Box 37, Folder 551)
  - 1995
    - Tribute to Thomas M. Debevoise, 1995 February 7 (Box 37, Folder 552)
    - Nomination of John Dyson as Board Chairman, Historic Hudson Valley, 1995 February 27 (Box 37, Folder 553)
    - Second Annual Spring Gathering, The Pocantico Society of Historic Hudson Valley, 1995 May 16 (Box 37, Folder 554)
    - Acceptance of the National Parks Foundation's Theodore Roosevelt National Park Medal of Honor, 1995 May 23 (Box 37, Folder 555)
    - Acceptance of Chairman's Award, National Geographic Society, 1995 June 8 (Box 37, Folder 556)
    - Cousin's Weekend: Remarks, 1995 June 17 (Box 37, Folder 557)
    - DeWitt Wallace Symposium in the Biomedical Sciences, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1995 October 11 (Box 37, Folder 558)
    - Presentation of the John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Founder's Award, Historic Hudson Valley, 1995 November 14 (Box 37, Folder 559)
      Award presented to George V. Grune.
    - Rockefeller Family Christmas Party, 1995 December 17 (Box 37, Folder 560)
  - 1996
    - Remarks Prior to Service at the Family Cemetery for Mrs. David (Margaret McGrath) Rockefeller, 1996 March 29 (Box 37, Folder 561)
    - Presentation of the John French Property to the National Park Service, 1996 June 7 (Box 37, Folder 562)
      Presentation made to Roger G. Kennedy, Director of the National Park Service.
    - Tribute to the Rev. Dr. Warren W. Ost, 45th National Board Meeting, A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1996 September 13 (Box 37, Folder 563)
    - Presentation of Laurance Spelman Rockefeller Conservation Award for Distinguished Service to Lady Bird Johnson, 1996 October 11 (Box 37, Folder 564)
      Award given by The Woodstock Foundation, Inc.
    - Presentation of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Founder's Award, Historic Hudson Valley, 1996 November 12 (Box 37, Folder 565)
      Award presented to Mrs. Brooke Astor.
  - 1997
    - Memorial Tribute to Mary French Rockefeller at First Congregational Church, Woodstock, Vermont, 1997 August 10 (Box 37, Folder 566)
    - Acceptance of Teton Award, 1997 September 10 (Box 37, Folder 567)
    - Presentation of Portrait of Lady Bird Johnson to the National Wildflower Center; Acceptance of Lady Bird Conservation Award for Lifetime Achievement, 1997 September 20 (Box 37, Folder 568)
    - Acceptance of the 1997 Governor's Parks and Preservation Award, 1997 December 13 (Box 37, Folder 569)
    - Dedication of Mary F. Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1997 December 16 (Box 37, Folder 570)
  - 1998
    - Ruth Fowler Retirement, Room 5600, Rockefeller Family and Associates, 1998 January 29 (Box 37, Folder 571)
    - Opening Ceremonies of Marsh-Billings National Historical Park, 1998 June 5 (Box 37, Folder 572)
    - Dinner to Honor James D. Robinson III, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1998 September 28 (Box 37, Folder 573)
    - Dedication of Rockwood Hall State Park, 1998 October 15 (Box 37, Folder 574)
      Inclusion of Rockwood Hall into the New York State Park System.
  - 1999
    - Dedication of the Laurance S. Rockefeller Outpatient Pavilion, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1999 April 19 (Box 37, Folder 575)
    - Acceptance of Award for Philanthropy, Awards for Excellence Dinner, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1999 May 18 (Box 37, Folder 576)
    - Statement for Dinner Honoring Gil Grosvenor, 1999 June 2 (Box 37, Folder 577)
    - Ethan Hitchcock's 90th Birthday, 1999 July 12 (Box 37, Folder 578)
    - Dedication of the Carriage Barn Visitor Center, Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park, 1999 August 7 (Box 37, Folder 579)
    - Dedication of the Integrative Medicine Outpatient Center, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1999 October 27 (Box 37, Folder 580)
  - 2000
    - Dinner Honoring Dr. Paul A. Marks, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 2000 January 13 (Box 38, Folder 581)
    - Tribute to Benno C. Schmidt, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 2000 March 20 (Box 38, Folder 582)
    - 10th Anniversary Celebration, Center for Human Values, Princeton University, 2000 April 27 (Box 38, Folder 583)
    - Funeral Service for Rodman Clark Rockefeller, The Riverside Church, 2000 May 18 (Box 38, Folder 584)
    - Matthew O. Case and Suzanne Engler Wedding, 2000 June 3 (Box 38, Folder 585)
    - Birthday Toast to Mrs. Rhoda Teagle, 2000 June 9 (Box 38, Folder 586)
    - Celebration of Laurance S. Rockefeller and David Rockefeller Birthdays, Family Weekend, Pocantico Hills: Laurance S. Rockefeller response, 2000 June 17 (Box 38, Folder 587)
    - Announcement of Joint Research Venture, Cornell University, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, and Rockefeller University, 2000 June 27 (Box 38, Folder 588)
    - 50th Anniversary Celebration, Grand Teton National Park, 2000 August 11 (Box 38, Folder 589)
    - Retirement of Hugh Powell, Room 5600, 2000 October 25 (Box 38, Folder 590)
      Hugh Powell worked at the Security Desk.
  - 2001
    - Central Park Conservancy Benefit, 2001 May 16 (Box 38, Folder 591)
      Benefit also included welcome of new President, Regina Peruggi.
    - Videotaped Greeting for Albert H. Gordon's 100th Birthday, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 2001 June 14 (Box 38, Folder 592)
    - Message to the University of Vermont-Montpelier Symposium on Environmental Ethics, 2001 November 2 (Box 38, Folder 593)
      Message was delivered by David A. Donath, President of the Woodstock Foundation, Inc.
  - 2002
    - Elizabeth J. McCormack's 80th Birthday Celebration, Room 5600, 2002 March 7 (Box 38, Folder 594)
    - Reception for Bill Moyers' Hudson Valley Series, 2002 April 10 (Box 38, Folder 595)
    - Healing Energy and Healing Intention Research Philanthropist Meeting, 2002 May 1-3 (Box 38, Folder 596)
    - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Founder's Award Gala, Historic Hudson Valley, 2002 November 12 (Box 38, Folder 597)
      Presentation of Founder's Award to Richard D. Parsons.
    - Rockefeller Family Christmas Luncheon: "Creating two Preeminent Institutions: The Legacy of Bessie Dashiell", 2002 December 15 (Box 38, Folder 598)
      Restricted Material: Material in the Rockefeller family collections which provides the names, correspondence or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net worth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted from scholarly access.